Noam Bassous

Second-year software engineering student at Shenkar and intelligence analyst after three-year military service in 8200 Unit. Proficiency in multitasking, teamwork, working under pressure and working with technological software. Highly motivated and ambitious with an open mind, excellent communication skills, and analytical thinking.

noambassous@gmail.com 054-7722438 Tirza 5, Ramat - Gan 22/07/1998

Skill Highlights

- Leadership and Teamwork
- Analytical skills
- Self-discipline
- Interpersonal skills
- Innovative
- Working under pressure
- Outside-the-box thinking
- High motivation
- Problem solving

Languages

Hebrew – Native Proficiency **English** – Professional Working Proficiency **Arabic** – Professional Working Proficiency

Volunteering

- 2012 2013: "Latet" organization
- 2013-2015:
 "Krembo Wings" A youth
 movement that integrates
 children and youth from
 general and special education

Education

Software Engineering Student at Shenkar

- Passed the first year with distinction (average grade: 94)
- Checked the homework of first-year students in Digital Systems course
- Providing tutoring and guidance to a first-year student in a programming course
- programming language skills:
 C, C++, HTML, CSS, PHP

Exclusive pre-military course and professional courses at 8200 unit

- Learning Arabic from scratch to full professional proficiency
- Various professional courses enhancing linguistics and analytic skills
- Acquiring abilities to supervise other soldiers' work on the most classified materials

Blich high school, Ramat Gan

- Full High school diploma
- 5 units English, 5 units Arabic, 5 units Physics, 4 units Math and 5 units Talmudic Literature
- Acknowledgement of Social Excellence

Experience

October 2020 to June 2021

Customer Service Representative at CAL

- Creating tailor-made solutions for customers' problems on a daily basis
- Providing helpful information, answering questions, and responding to customers' complaints on various platforms
- Working with great responsibility in the financial sphere

December 2018 September 2019

Team Leader at 8200 Unit

- Leading a team of 10+ soldiers on both professional and personal levels
- Assigning workload and projects based on soldiers' knowledge and skills
- Supervising training and apprenticeship of new soldiers

August 2016 to September 2019

Sigint Intelligence Analyst at 8200 Unit

- Integrate information from various data sources to provide an information need, routinely and under special circumstances and urgent operations
- Write professional intelligence summaries and analyses of intelligence materials in multiple classification levels
- Work with various intelligence software for collecting and preserving information
- Providing professional input for senior officials and officers